{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315943786","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315943785"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_104529"," gameId":" d762f63e-5696-42e8-919c-0d8fc81be0de"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_M-Z-N"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315990036","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315990036"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_104529"," gameId":" 5822d2c8-9708-4dd5-bd12-238fb469a9e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chekechea_miiba-tupu-kituo-chekechea"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" chekechea"," userResponse":" kituo"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548315992712","data":{"timestamp":" 1548315992712"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_104529"," gameId":" 5822d2c8-9708-4dd5-bd12-238fb469a9e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chekechea_miiba-tupu-kituo-chekechea"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" chekechea"," userResponse":" chekechea"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316037871","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316037871"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_104529"," gameId":" 5822d2c8-9708-4dd5-bd12-238fb469a9e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" huzuni_refu-huzuni-jina-msitu"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" huzuni"," userResponse":" jina"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316041372","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316041371"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_104529"," gameId":" 5822d2c8-9708-4dd5-bd12-238fb469a9e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" huzuni_refu-huzuni-jina-msitu"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" huzuni"," userResponse":" msitu"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316044333","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316044332"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_104529"," gameId":" 5822d2c8-9708-4dd5-bd12-238fb469a9e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" huzuni_refu-huzuni-jina-msitu"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" huzuni"," userResponse":" refu"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316047413","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316047413"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_104529"," gameId":" 5822d2c8-9708-4dd5-bd12-238fb469a9e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" huzuni_refu-huzuni-jina-msitu"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" huzuni"," userResponse":" huzuni"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316075613","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316075613"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_104529"," gameId":" 5822d2c8-9708-4dd5-bd12-238fb469a9e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chekechea_ngozi-mali-chekechea-yuko"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" chekechea"," userResponse":" chekechea"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316097264","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316097264"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_104529"," gameId":" 5822d2c8-9708-4dd5-bd12-238fb469a9e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chekechea_sita-mfereji-chekechea-pango"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" chekechea"," userResponse":" chekechea"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316128066","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316128066"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_104529"," gameId":" 5822d2c8-9708-4dd5-bd12-238fb469a9e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kubwa_nyanya-hadi-nyingine-kubwa"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" kubwa"," userResponse":" kubwa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316157913","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316157913"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_104529"," gameId":" 5822d2c8-9708-4dd5-bd12-238fb469a9e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chupa_barua-chupa-chai-kumbe"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" chupa"," userResponse":" chupa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316206695","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316206695"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_104529"," gameId":" 5822d2c8-9708-4dd5-bd12-238fb469a9e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mahali_mamake-mbali-nyumba-mahali"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" mahali"," userResponse":" mahali"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316227510","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316227510"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_104529"," gameId":" 5822d2c8-9708-4dd5-bd12-238fb469a9e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ambia_endelea-majuto-Ambia-maringo"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" Ambia"," userResponse":" majuto"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316230899","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316230899"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_104529"," gameId":" 5822d2c8-9708-4dd5-bd12-238fb469a9e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ambia_endelea-majuto-Ambia-maringo"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" Ambia"," userResponse":" Ambia"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316283880","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316283880"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_104529"," gameId":" 5822d2c8-9708-4dd5-bd12-238fb469a9e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sana_kwenda-wakati-za-sana"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" sana"," userResponse":" sana"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316512406","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316512406"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_104529"," gameId":" 5822d2c8-9708-4dd5-bd12-238fb469a9e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" sana_kwenda-wakati-za-sana"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316512574","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316512574"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_104529"," gameId":" 5822d2c8-9708-4dd5-bd12-238fb469a9e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Soma tena hadithi kisha ujibu maswali haya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAYA"," userResponse":" HAYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316522757","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316522757"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_104529"," gameId":" 14e609d3-62e5-4de2-8994-34cf39f8e213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" HELIKOPTA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HELIKOPTA"," userResponse":" HELIKOPTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316528248","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316528248"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_104529"," gameId":" 14e609d3-62e5-4de2-8994-34cf39f8e213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" HELIKOPTA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HELIKOPTA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316529814","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316529814"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_104529"," gameId":" 14e609d3-62e5-4de2-8994-34cf39f8e213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" HARUFU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HARUFU"," userResponse":" HARUFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316533724","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316533724"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_104529"," gameId":" 14e609d3-62e5-4de2-8994-34cf39f8e213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" HARUFU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HARUFU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316535300","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316535300"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_104529"," gameId":" 14e609d3-62e5-4de2-8994-34cf39f8e213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" HUJAMBO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUJAMBO"," userResponse":" HUJAMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316539833","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316539833"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_104529"," gameId":" 14e609d3-62e5-4de2-8994-34cf39f8e213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" HUJAMBO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUJAMBO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316541478","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316541478"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_104529"," gameId":" 14e609d3-62e5-4de2-8994-34cf39f8e213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" HARAKA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HARAKA"," userResponse":" HARAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316545146","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316545145"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_104529"," gameId":" 14e609d3-62e5-4de2-8994-34cf39f8e213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" HARAKA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HARAKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316546718","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316546718"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_104529"," gameId":" 14e609d3-62e5-4de2-8994-34cf39f8e213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" HARUSI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HARUSI"," userResponse":" HARUSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316551042","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316551042"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_104529"," gameId":" 14e609d3-62e5-4de2-8994-34cf39f8e213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" HARUSI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HARUSI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316552607","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316552607"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_104529"," gameId":" 14e609d3-62e5-4de2-8994-34cf39f8e213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" HOSPITALI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HOSPITALI"," userResponse":" HOSPITALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316556993","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316556993"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_104529"," gameId":" 14e609d3-62e5-4de2-8994-34cf39f8e213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" HOSPITALI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HOSPITALI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316558550","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316558550"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_104529"," gameId":" 14e609d3-62e5-4de2-8994-34cf39f8e213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" HUNYWA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUNYWA"," userResponse":" HUNYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316562253","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316562253"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_104529"," gameId":" 14e609d3-62e5-4de2-8994-34cf39f8e213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" HUNYWA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUNYWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316563805","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316563805"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_104529"," gameId":" 14e609d3-62e5-4de2-8994-34cf39f8e213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" HOHO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HOHO"," userResponse":" HOHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316567211","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316567211"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_104529"," gameId":" 14e609d3-62e5-4de2-8994-34cf39f8e213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" HOHO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HOHO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316568805","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316568805"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_104529"," gameId":" 14e609d3-62e5-4de2-8994-34cf39f8e213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" HEMA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HEMA"," userResponse":" HEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316571943","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316571943"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_104529"," gameId":" 14e609d3-62e5-4de2-8994-34cf39f8e213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" HEMA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HEMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316573496","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316573495"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_104529"," gameId":" 14e609d3-62e5-4de2-8994-34cf39f8e213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" HASIRA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HASIRA"," userResponse":" HASIRA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316577175","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316577175"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_104529"," gameId":" 14e609d3-62e5-4de2-8994-34cf39f8e213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" HASIRA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HASIRA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316579191","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316579190"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_104529"," gameId":" 14e609d3-62e5-4de2-8994-34cf39f8e213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" HASIRA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548316579358","data":{"timestamp":" 1548316579357"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_104529"," gameId":" 14e609d3-62e5-4de2-8994-34cf39f8e213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" HASIRA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HASIRA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}